

Dedicated and loyal custodian with over 20 years of experience in maintaining and cleaning buildings. Able to efficiently handle a variety of cleaning and repair projects.

Dependable and physically fit Fluent in Spanish and English. Willing to work additional shiftsand on weekends or holidays.

Professional Experience

Custodian

Jackson Street Office Park, Austin, TX October 2010- Present

- Sweep, mop, and sanitize bathrooms, offices, reception areas, and lounges
- Empty trash cans and recyclable receptacles in restrooms and offices
- · Carry out minor building repairsas required
- · Wash windowsand outdoor areas on a regular schedule
- Manage a team of six additional cleaners and maintenance staff
- Strictly follow company procedures and policies to ensure a safe and clean working environment
- Monitor cleaning supply stocksand order additional supplies as required

Custodian

Apple Tree Middle School. Austin, TX July 1999 - September 2010

- Sole custodian in a 100+ student middle school
- Received 11 commendations for dependability and friendliness
- Awarded Employee of the Year on two occasions
- Received multiple thank you letters from students, staff, and parents for going above the call of duty
- Ensured stocks of cleaning and restroom supplies
- Mo pped, c lea ned, a nd swe pt c lassroo ms, offices, a nd co rri d o rs
- · Cleaned and sanitized restrooms
- Assisted in setup and teardown forevents such as sporting competitions, awards ceremonies, and parent-teacher conferences
- Removed trash to the appropriate disposal area
- ♦ Carried out minor building repairs

456 Main Street, Austin, TX 12345 j.cross^you re mail.com (123)456-7890

Education

High School Diploma Jackson High School, Austin,TX, September 1995 - June 1999

Key Skills

- Organized
- Punctual
- · Physically Fit
- Friendly
- Knowledge of a Variety of Chemicals
- Team Leader
- Hard Working